maclegion.com 2013-09-20

# MacLegion.com Privacy Policy

## Hate spam? So do we!

When you purchase an offer or register for a free promotional event from MacLegion, we share your name and email address with the respective developer/publisher/manufacturer (MacLegion partner). This is done for two reasons; to accurately register you as a valid buyer of the product with the MacLegion partner; to generate your serial numbers (many serial numbers are based on your name and/or email address to protect against piracy). This ensures that you’ll receive full after sales support and upgrade paths from all MacLegion partners as though you’d purchased the software directly from them. As a result, MacLegion partners may email you with first-party offers from time to time as they would any of their customers; all partners must support and respect any opt-out requests from future communications made by you, and are also required to provide opt-out links in any correspondence they send you.

## We respect your privacy!

In order to view our site, it is not necessary that you provide us with any personally identifiable information. However, access to account features requires that you provide personally identifiable information. We require users who wish to purchase products and/or services from our website to create a free membership account. MacLegion will never sell, distribute, rent or share any of your personally identifiable information. We recognize that many visitors to our site are concerned about the information they may provide to us, and how we treat that information. For this reason, we utilize industry standard security and encryption technologies for the storage of any personally identifiable information. Furthermore, we do not store or retain any credit card, PayPal and/or any other payment/billing information.

* Any changes to this Privacy Policy shall be effective immediately following the posting of such changes on our website. For this reason, we encourage you to check this Privacy Policy from time to time.
